odurinde.co.uk 2014-09-29

# The Privacy Policy | Odurinde Finance & Business Blog

We emphasize on the security of the details and information that we attain from various individuals. We believe that protecting their personal details is our sole responsibility. The usual practices of the websites on the attained information are vividly mentioned in the page. The policies we abide by when it comes to privacy are applicable to all our users and include all the other websites that are connected to us by any sort of subsidiary alliance. However the browsers are requested to review the page frequently so that they can find out the changes brought in the policy. If in any case a user finds any of the policies mentioned inappropriate then he is free to terminate the usage of this website. You can also go to our [terms & conditions](http://www.odurinde.co.uk/terms-conditions/) page for more information.

_**Applicability of the privacy policy**_

According to the privacy policy of our website, we are permitted to use the information that we attain from all our users. But we are not permitted nor do we indulge in sharing of essential and private information of a user to the third party websites that are linked to us. They have their own set pf privacy policies and do not interfere into ours. We are not responsible for their policies and are not liable if your information is put to use by such sites.

_**Personal Information of the visitors**_

While you visit our website we collect your internet address at that very moment and the operating system you are using as well as the browsing software that is being used by you. Apart from that we can also track the pages that you are visiting in our website. We simply collect all these information, make an aggregate document which enables us to enrich ourselves in experience and allow us to know the users better. These information allow us to remain updated especially stuff those pages most popular with more information. All these are however performed without even knowing the identity of yours. Usually all the visitors remain anonymous to us unless you yourself choose to let yourself known to us.

If any of you are willing to share your personal details with us then we can ensure that none of these will be leaked but will remain secured and kept safe in our database. We don’t indulge in exchanging, renting or even selling of the information that you have provided us with.

_**Privacy details**_

We do not use any sort of encrypted data in our website. There are certain websites that demand for your confidential details like

  * Social security number,
  * PIN number of your debit card
  * Credit card number etc, then it must be checked out by the visitor if the data is being taken in encrypted form or not. This encryption of data allows the information to remain confidential. However, it is always advised that you send such highly personal numbers through emails or cell phone messages.

_**Information about minor users**_

We are not keen in collecting information about the details of any minor user who is aged below eighteen years of age. However we do emphasize on the importance of the permission of their guardians before they share their personal information with us. [Click here](http://www.odurinde.co.uk/) to go back to the home page.

## Finance | Money | Insurance | Credit | Personal Fanance | Mortage | Stock | Business | Shopping
